<resources>
    <string name="s_project_name">Karya</string>
    <string name="s_no_internet_or_server_down">We are not able to reach our server. Please ensure you have internet turned on.</string>
    <string name="s_click_to_retry">Click this button to retry</string>
    <string name="s_unknown_error">Unknown error occurred. Please close the application and open again. If error persists, contact your project coordinator</string>
    <string name="s_salutation">Hi</string>
    <string name="s_show_app_in_language">Show the app in English</string>
    <string name="s_prompt_for_language_select">To show app in English, press here</string>
    <string name="s_fetching_values_for_language">Getting all necessary data to display the app in English</string>
    <string name="s_consent_form_title">Consent Form</string>
    <string name="s_access_code_title">Enter Access Code</string>
    <string name="s_otp_title">Enter OTP</string>
    <string name="s_phone_number_title">Enter Phone Number</string>
    <string name="s_age_title">Enter Year of Birth</string>
    <string name="s_gender_title">Select Gender</string>
    <string name="s_profile_pic_title">Select Profile Picture</string>
    <string name="s_dashboard_title">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="s_consent_form_agree">I agree</string>
    <string name="s_consent_form_disagree">No. I do not want to participate</string>
    <string name="s_consent_form_text"><![CDATA[
    <h5>Participant Privacy Policy</h5>
    <p>This privacy policy (<b>Privacy Policy</b>) will help you understand what information we collect for the Project, why we collect it, how we
            will use it, including if and how we share the information with third parties, and the choices you have with
            respect to your information. When we talk about &ldquo;we,&rdquo; &ldquo;our,&rdquo; or &ldquo;us&rdquo; in
            this Privacy Policy, we are referring to Navana Tech India Private Limited (<b>Navana
            Tech</b>). When we talk about &ldquo;you&rdquo; in this Privacy Policy, we are referring
            to the participant / voice data contributor.
    </p>        
    <br>
    <p>By agreeing to the Speech Recognition in Agriculture and Finance for the Poor in
            India - Consent Form,&nbsp;you expressly agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy,
            for your use of Navana Tech&#39;s voice data collection application (<b>
           App</b>) and for the collection, processing, storage, use, disclosure,
            transfer and otherwise handling of your personal and sensitive personal data in accordance with the terms
            contained below. &nbsp;You have the option to not provide your sensitive personal data (as defined under
            applicable law) to us, or withdraw consent once provided, however, we will not be able to provide you with
            access to the App in case you elect to do so and further would be unable to process payment to you. If you
            do not wish to provide us with your sensitive personal data please do not use the App and uninstall it from
            your devices. &nbsp; &nbsp;
    </p>
    <br>
    <p>We may revise the Privacy Policy from time to time. While we may not be able to
            separately notify you of the revisions each time that we make them, we will notify you and obtain your
            consent for any changes that we make to this policy when required under law. We encourage you to check this
            page periodically for modifications or revisions to the Privacy Policy to understand how it affects the use
            of your information.
    </p>
    <br>
    <p>Any personal information collected in accordance with this Privacy Policy will be
            collected and retained by us.</p>
    <br>
    <ol start="1">
        <li>INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND RECEIVE</li>
    </ol>
    <br>
    <ol start="1">
        <li>Personal Information Collected from You </li>
    </ol>
    <br>
    <ul>
        <li>Registration Information: The registration
                process may require you to sign-in with your phone number. This information will be used to identify you
                on the platform when you close the App and open it again. The App will also ask you to choose a profile
                picture. This picture will only be used for display in the App and will not be stored on our
                platform.</li>
    </ul>
    <br>
    <ul>
        <li>Demographic Data:&nbsp;We will collect some
                demographic information about you, e.g., your age range, gender, education level, the State you are in,
                your mother tongue and languages you can read, write and speak, for research related purposes and to
                improve our algorithm. </li>
    </ul>
    <br>
    <ul>
        <li>Identity Verification Information:&nbsp;We
                also collect your name and PAN card details for the purposes of mapping with your voice sample and for
                other administrative purposes. &nbsp;</li>
    </ul>
    <br>
    <ul>
        <li>Location Information:&nbsp;We may collect
                your geographical location which will be restricted to an area of a village. We will not however require
                your GPS coordinates.</li>
    </ul>
    <br>
    <ul>
        <li>Information for the purpose of promotion/posters: <span
               >We may use pictures from the study in presentations or posters without identifying specific
                individuals. We will request your permission before taking pictures and obtain your permission to use
                those pictures in our presentations or posters. Not providing consent for taking pictures will not
                disqualify you from participating in the study.</li>
    </ul>
    <br>
    <ol start="2">
        <li>Sensitive Personal Information collected from you:</li>
    </ol>
    <br>
    <ul>
        <li>Password Information:&nbsp;To begin, you
                will be introduced to the Project Coordinator for your location. This person will be your point of
                contact for help related to the project. Your project coordinator will provide you with instructions and
                if necessary, help you download and install the App on your smartphone. Your project coordinator will
                give you a &quot;16-digit Access Code&quot;. You need to enter the code during the registration process.
                Each access code can be used only once. Therefore, do not share the access code with anyone else.
            </li>
    </ul>
    <br>
    <p>Payment Information:&nbsp;You will be paid for all
            correctly completed tasks on the platform. We will pay you periodically for all your tasks that have
            undergone quality verification. You will be paid up to Rs. 15 per validated sentence submitted and up to
            Rs. 1 per validated audio file submitted. The financial information we collect for the purpose of payment may include
            information such as your credit card number, your debit card number, your bank account number, bank IFSC
            code, your UPI handle, payment wallet information and net-banking details. The information we collect would
            depend on the payment method that you use. We may pass this information on to our third-party payment
            services vendors, or these entities may also directly collect this information from you. We will collect and
            store your payment information for the duration of the study. We will delete all payment information as soon
            as your participation is completed. Please contact your project coordinator if you have any queries
            regarding payments. We will not store this information, if we are not permitted under applicable law.
            &nbsp;</p>
    <br>
    <ul>
        <li>Health Related Information:&nbsp;We may
                collect certain health related information about you such as if you have been diagnosed with any speech
                related disorders in the past and if you are on any medications to treat the disorder. We will require
                you to answer questions in relation to speech disorders as either yes or no.</li>
    </ul>
    <br>
    <ol start="3">
        <li>Non-Personal Information: </li>
    </ol>
    <br>
    <ul>
        <li>Feedback information:&nbsp;<span
               >After the end of the study, we may request a short interview with you to gather your feedback
                and understand your experience of using our platform.</li>
    </ul>
    <br>
    <ul>
        <li>Dataset Information:&nbsp;Datasets will
                contain only text or audio data that is not associated with personally identifiable information and will
                be used to create speech recognition technology. If you have any questions regarding how the dataset
                will be used, please feel free to ask through your project coordinator.</li>
    </ul>
    <br>
    <p>B.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;PURPOSE OF COLLECTION</p>
    <br>
    <p>Any personal information we collect during the study will only be used to identify
            you during the duration of the study. </p>
    <br>
    <p>Purpose of collection:</p>
    <br>
    <p>We use personal information of Users for the following purposes: </p>
    <br>
    <ul>
        <li>Administrative and Legal Purposes:<span
               >&nbsp;We will access and use your data as reasonably necessary to (a)
                provide, maintain and improve the App; (b) prevent or address service, security, technical issues, or at
                your request in connection with support matters; © act in a manner required by law; (d) register you
                with the App and complete identity verification; (e) to enable payments to you; (f) to create datasets
                as mentioned above for open access; and (g) act in the manner expressly permitted in writing by
                you.</li>
    </ul>
    <br>
    <ul>
        <li>To improve our App and Services:&nbsp;We
                will access and use your data to carry out research and analyze trends to better improve our algorithm.
            </li>
    </ul>
    <br>
    <ul>
        <li>We will access and use your data for other purposes you consent to,
                are notified of, or are disclosed when you provide personal information.</li>
    </ul>
    <br>
    <p>At the end of your participation, we request you to delete the application from your
            phone. Should you want, your project coordinator will aid you in uninstalling, configuring, and deleting the
            application.</p>

    <br>
    <p>C.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;YOUR CHOICES <span
           >Access to Personal Data or Information</p>
    <br>
    <p>You will have the right, upon request, to access, change, modify and review the
            personal information provided by you and held by us. Upon discovering that the information provided is
            inaccurate or deficient in any manner, you will have the right to request suitable changes or amendments to
            such information, which will be carried out by us, when feasible. </p>
    <br>
    <p>You will also have the option of withdrawing consent by reaching out to us at
        <a
                href="mailto:operations@navanatech.in">operations@navanatech.in</a>. However,
            exercising this option will hamper our ability to provide you with any or all of the features of the
            App.</p>
    
    <br>
    <p>D.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;SHARING AND DISCLOSURE </p>

    <br>
    <p>We will not publish or disclose your personal information without your prior
            consent, unless we are required to do so in order to facilitate use of the App, it is for the Purposes (as
            indicated in Part B), it is mandated by law, or if you have previously provided your consent. We may
            disclose personal information with our employees, officers, agents, consultants, business associates,
            contractors, attorneys, etc., on a need-to-know basis for the Purposes. </p>

   <br>
    <p>We will disclose any sensitive personal data and information if there is a legal
            requirement or if we are ordered to do so by a court of competent jurisdiction or to any government agency
            if required by law for the purposes of verification of identity, or for prevention, detection, or
            investigation of crime (including cyber incidents), or for prosecution or punishment of offences.</p>

    <br>
    <p>E.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;TRANSFER</p>
    <br>
    <p>We do not transfer personal information pertaining to you to third parties.
    </p>

    <br>
    <p>F.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;SECURITY</p>
    <br>
    <p>We ensure the confidentiality and security of the personal information and sensitive
            personal data and information provided by you by implementing comprehensive information security practices
            and standards as mandated by the Data Protection Rules. </p>

    <br>
    <p>G.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;GRIEVANCE OFFICER</p>
    <br>
    <p>Should you have any questions in relation to this Privacy Policy , you may address
            them to our grievance officer whose name and email address are as follows:</p>
    <p>[&#9679;] Raoul Nanavati</p>
    <p>[&#9679;] operations@navanatech.in</p>
    <br>
    <p>&nbsp; In case you do not have access to email, you can contact your project
            coordinator, and have them relay your concerns to the grievance officer.</p>
    ]]></string>

    <string name="s_consent_form_summary">Summary of the consent form</string>
    <string name="s_access_code_prompt">Enter 16-digit access code</string>
    <string name="s_download_prompt">Please Wait. Downloading files and other assets.</string>
    <string name="s_invalid_creation_code">You have entered an invalid creation code.</string>
    <string name="s_creation_code_already_used">The creation code you have entered is already used. Please contact your project coordinator.</string>
    <string name="s_phone_number_prompt">Enter your 10-digit mobile number</string>
    <string name="s_sending_otp">Sending OTP to your phone</string>
    <string name="s_unable_to_send_otp">We were unable to send OTP to your number. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="s_otp_prompt">We have sent you a 6-digit OTP via SMS. Please enter that OTP below</string>
    <string name="s_invalid_otp">You have entered an invalid OTP</string>
    <string name="s_resend_otp">Resend OTP</string>
    <string name="s_profile_picture_prompt">Please click your profile picture. You can skip this step if you do not want a profile picture</string>
    <string name="s_gender_prompt">Please choose your gender. If you do not wish to state your gender, you can skip this step</string>
    <string name="s_male">Male</string>
    <string name="s_female">Female</string>
    <string name="s_age_prompt">Please enter your year of birth</string>
    <string name="s_years">years</string>
    <string name="s_registering_worker">Registering worker with the server</string>
    <string name="s_phone_number_already_used">Your phone number is already registered. Please try with another phone number.</string>
    <!-- TODO: update tick and cross with more suitable words -->
    <string name="s_skill_question_description">We have three questions about your skills in English. For each question, please click tick for yes, and cross for no.</string>
    <string name="s_read_skill_question">Can you read in English?</string>
    <string name="s_speak_skill_question">Can you speak in English?</string>
    <string name="s_type_skill_question">Can you type in English?</string>
    <string name="s_registering_skill">Registering new skill for worker</string>
    <string name="s_failed_to_register_skill">Failed to register new skill for worker</string>
    <string name="s_other_language_selection">If you know any other language, please select that language below</string>
    <string name="s_uploading_files">Uploading files to the box</string>
    <string name="s_send_updates">Sending updates to the box</string>
    <string name="s_receive_updates">Receiving updates from the box</string>
    <string name="s_downloading_files">Downloading files from the box</string>
    <string name="s_get_new_tasks"> Get new tasks</string>
    <string name="s_submit_completed_tasks">Submit completed tasks</string>
    <string name="s_update_verified_tasks">Update verified tasks</string>
    <string name="s_update_earning">Update earnings</string>
    <string name="s_tasks_available">tasks available</string>
    <string name="s_tasks_completed">tasks completed</string>
    <string name="s_tasks_submitted">tasks submitted</string>
    <string name="s_tasks_verified">tasks verified</string>
    <string name="d_tasks_available">%d/%d tasks available</string>
    <string name="d_tasks_completed">%d/%d tasks completed</string>
    <string name="d_tasks_submitted">%d/%d tasks submitted</string>
    <string name="d_tasks_verified">%d/%d tasks verified</string>
    <string name="s_update_app_language">Change the App Language</string>
    <string name="s_update_skills">Update Language Skills</string>
    <string name="s_sync_prompt_message">You have completed tasks that can be submitted to the server. Do you want to submit the tasks now?</string>
    <string name="s_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="s_no">No</string>
    <string name="s_speech_scenario_name">Speech-data Collection</string>
    <string name="s_speech_scenario_description">This task consists of a set of sentences. The worker is expected to record themselves reading out each sentence, one sentence at a time</string>
    <string name="s_story_scenario_name">Group Speech-data Collection</string>
    <string name="s_story_scenario_description">This task consists of a set of stories. The worker is expected to record themselves reading out each story, one sentence at a time</string>
    <string name="s_recording_scenario_name">Verification of Speech Data Recordings</string>
    <string name="s_recording_scenario_description">This task consists of a set of recordings. The worker is expected to verify the given recording and text.</string>
    <string name="s_record_sentence">You have to record yourself speaking out this sentence</string>
    <string name="s_record_action">To start recording, press this button. It will turn red indicating that the recording has started.</string>
    <string name="s_stop_action">Once you are done recording, press this button again to stop the recording</string>
    <string name="s_listen_action"> The app will play back the recorded audio. Listen to it carefully to ensure it is correct and that there is no other background voice.</string>
    <string name="s_rerecord_action">If your recording is not correct, you can record again using the record button.</string>
    <string name="s_next_action">If you are happy with the recording, you can press this button to go to the next sentence.</string>
    <string name="s_next">Next</string>
    <string name="s_previous_action"> You can press this button to go to the previous sentence.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="s_other">Other</string>
    <string name="d_sentences_available">%d sentences available</string>
    <string name="rupees_d">₹%d</string>
    <string name="refresh_underline"><u>Refresh</u></string>
    <string name="refreshing">Refreshing…</string>
    <string name="tasks_updated">Tasks Updated</string>
</resources>
